Garrison Family Papers, 1694-2005 (bulk 1830-1950)
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- SERIES III. CORRESPONDENCE 1744-1996
  - Family letters
    - Generation 4
      - Garrison, William Lloyd (1874)
        - Garrison
          - Eleanor 1888-1948, undated (Box 84, Folder 1)
          - Ellen Wright 1886-1931 (Box 84, Folder 2-7)
          - Francis Jackson 1914 (Box 84, Folder 8)
          - Frank Wright 1914-33, undated (Box 84, Folder 9)
          - John Bright 1926 (Box 84, Folder 10)
          - William Lloyd (1838) 1889-1909 (Box 84, Folder 11-12)
          - William Lloyd (1902) 1913-43 (Box 84, Folder 13)
        - Norton, Katherine Garrison 1923 (Box 85, Folder 1)
        - Stephenson
          - Barton 1929 (Box 85, Folder 2)
          - Benjamin 1918 (Box 85, Folder 3)
          - Walter 1921-31 (Box 85, Folder 4)
        - Valentine Alan 1940 (Box 85, Folder 5)
        - Villard
          - Fanny Garrison 1892 (Box 85, Folder 6)
          - Oswald Garrison 1884-1915 (Box 85, Folder 7)
        - Miscellaneous
          - A-Z 1908-24, undated (Box 85, Folder 8)
          - Letters to the editor and public officials 1916-30, undated (Box 85, Folder 9)
        - Unidentified 1909-41, undated (Box 85, Folder 10)
        - Outgoing
          - Indexes (Box 86, Folder 1)
            - 1922-24 (Box 86, Folder 2-9)
            - 1925-27 (Box 87, Folder 1-8)
            - 1928-30 (Box 88, Folder 1-8)
            - 1931-33 (Box 89, Folder 1-6)
      - Norton, Charles Dyer
        - Garrison
          - Francis Jackson 1908 (Box 90, Folder 1)
          - William Lloyd (1874) 1898-1922, undated (Box 90, Folder 2)
        - Norton, Harriet Dyer 1900 (Box 90, Folder 3)
        - Villard, Oswald Garrisoncirca 1911 (Box 90, Folder 4)
        - Unidentified 1896-97 (Box 90, Folder 5)
      - Norton, Katherine Garrison
        - Garrison
          - Agnes 1881-1940 (Box 90, Folder 6-12)
          - Edith Stephenson 1931, 1941 (Box 90, Folder 13)
          - Eleanor 1901-44, undated (Box 90, Folder 14)
          - Ellen Wright 1903, 1926, undated (Box 90, Folder 15)
          - Francis Jackson
            - 1885-1908 (Box 90, Folder 16-19)
            - 1909-13 (Box 91, Folder 1-8)
            - 1914-16 (Box 92, Folder 1-2)
          - Frank Wright 1900, undated (Box 92, Folder 3)
          - Philip McKim 1908 (Box 92, Folder 4)
          - Theresa Holmes 1911 (Box 92, Folder 5)
          - Wendell Phillips 1898-1904 (Box 92, Folder 6)
          - Willaim Lloyd (1838)1880 (Box 92, Folder 7)
          - William Lloyd (1874) 1896-1945, undated (Box 92, Folder 8)
        - Martin, Florence Hawes 1909 (Box 92, Folder 9)
        - Norton
          - Charles Dyer 1907-22 (Box 92, Folder 10-11)
          - Charles McKim 1939, 1940 (Box 92, Folder 12)
          - Garrison 1914-41 (Box 92, Folder 13)
          - Harriet Dyer 1896-1921 (Box 92, Folder 14)
        - Valentine
          - Alan 1933, undated (Box 92, Folder 15)
          - Lucia Norton 1930-45 (Box 92, Folder 16-17)
        - Villard
          - Fanny Garrison 1923, undated (Box 93, Folder 1)
          - Oswald Garrison 1886, undated (Box 93, Folder 2)
        - Wood, Alice Cox 1899 (Box 93, Folder 3)
        - Miscellaneous
          - "Children" and "Boys" 1920, 1924 (Box 93, Folder 4)
          - Letters dictated from Beverly Hospital6 Jul-8 Aug 1910 (Box 93, Folder 5-6)
          - Unidentified and fragments 1920-41, undated (Box 93, Folder 7)
          - Katherine Garrison Norton Letters, 1881-1945 edited by Lucia Norton Valentine, 4 vol.undated (Box 94)
      - Villard
        - Garrison 1939 (Box 95, Folder 1)
        - Harold 1897-1944 (Box 95, Folder 2)
        - Helen 1883 (Box 95, Folder 3)
        - Julia 1935, undated (Box 95, Folder 4)
        - Mariquita Serrano 1895, undated (Box 95, Folder 5)
        - Oswald Garrison
          - Clark, Roger 1942-49 (Box 95, Folder 6)
          - Garrison
            - Agnes 1895-43 (Box 95, Folder 7)
            - Charles 1883 (Box 95, Folder 8)
            - David Lloyd 1924-46, undated (Box 95, Folder 9)
            - Eleanor 1948 (Box 95, Folder 10)
            - Ellen Wright 1915-30 (Box 95, Folder 11)
            - Francis Jackson 1903-14 (Box 95, Folder 12)
            - William Lloyd (1838) 1891-1909 (Box 95, Folder 13)
            - William Lloyd (1874) and Edith Stephenson 1897-1949, undated (Box 96, Folder 1-16)
        - Hilgard, Alice 1927 (Box 96, Folder 17)
        - Wager, Charles H. A. 1920 (Box 96, Folder 18)
    - Generation 5
      - Auchincloss, Lydia Garrison 1958 (Box 97, Folder 1)
      - Binger, Clarinda ("Cloë") Garrison 1926 (Box 97, Folder 2)
      - Bliss, Edith ("Yoy") Garrison
        - Garrison
          - Agnes 1919, 1922 (Box 97, Folder 3)
          - David Lloyd 1925-49, undated (Box 97, Folder 4)
          - Eleanor 1968 (Box 97, Folder 5)
          - Ellen Wright 1922, undated (Box 97, Folder 6)
          - Frank Wright 1958 (Box 97, Folder 7)
          - William Lloyd (1874) and Edith Stephenson 1921-69, undated (Box 97, Folder 8-12)
        - Unidentified 1967, undated (Box 97, Folder 13)
      - Emerson, Claire ("Tita") Garrison
        - Bliss, Edith ("Yoy") Garrison 1934, undated (Box 97, Folder 14)
        - Garrison
          - Agnes 1922-45, undated (Box 97, Folder 15)
          - David Lloyd and Alice ("Patty") 1921-77, undated (Box 97, Folder 16)
          - Eleanor 1958-72, undated (Box 97, Folder 17)
          - Ellen Wright 1913-31 (Box 97, Folder 18)
          - John Bright 1923-25 (Box 97, Folder 19)
          - William Lloyd (1874) and Edith Stephenson
            - 1911-25 (Box 98, Folder 1-7)
            - 1926-35 (Box 99, Folder 1-7)
            - 1936-69, undated (Box 100, Folder 1-8)
        - Grierson, Margaret Storrs 1963-67 (Box 101, Folder 1)
        - Harwood, Faith Garrison 1931-34 (Box 101, Folder 2)
        - Stephenson, Luda Grant 1919, 1928 (Box 101, Folder 3)
        - Miscellaneous family 1957 (Box 101, Folder 4)
      - Emerson, Robert 1928, 1938 (Box 101, Folder 5)
      - Garrison, Alice ('Patty")
        - David Lloyd 1944-48, undated (Box 101, Folder 6)
        - Miscellaneous family 1945-77 (Box 101, Folder 7)
      - Garrison, Barbara Foss 1941-44, undated (Box 101, Folder 8)
      - Garrison, Catherine Cooper 1927-65 (Box 101, Folder 9)
      - Garrison, David Lloyd
        - Bliss, Edith Garrison ("Yoy") 1921-86 (Box 101, Folder 10)
        - Daniel, Yi Yi 1928-47, undated (Box 101, Folder 11)
        - Garrison
          - Agnes 1929, undated (Box 101, Folder 12)
          - Eleanor 1858-65 (Box 101, Folder 13)
          - Frank Wright 1957-60 (Box 101, Folder 14)
          - William Lloyd (1874) and Edith Stephensoncirca 1910-58, undated (Box 102, Folder 1-11)
          - Miscellaneous family 1914-67, undated (Box 102, Folder 12)
          - Miscellaneous 1943-45 (Box 102, Folder 13)
      - Garrison, George Anthony and Nancy McGilpin
        - Garrison, Eleanor 1961-64 (Box 103, Folder 1)
        - Grierson, Margaret Storrs 1967-96, undated (Box 103, Folder 2)
      - Garrison, John Bright
        - Garrison
          - David Lloyd 1928-45 (Box 103, Folder 3-4)
          - Eleanor 1962-70 (Box 103, Folder 5)
          - Frank Wright 1956-61 (Box 103, Folder 6)
          - William Lloyd (1874) and Edith Stephenson 1921-58, undated (Box 104, Folder 1-5)
          - Miscellaneous family 1921-43 (Box 104, Folder 6)
      - Garrison, Lloyd Kirkham 1906-59 (Box 104, Folder 7)
      - Garrison, Rhoda 1962-92 (Box 104, Folder 8)
      - Garrison, Rhodes 1955-58 (Box 104, Folder 9)
      - Garrison, Ritchie 1968 (Box 104, Folder 10)
      - Garrison, Robert Hale 1910-73, undated (Box 104, Folder 11)
      - Garrison, William Lloyd (1902) and Jane Wilson
        - Emerson, Claire ("Tita") 1924 (Box 104, Folder 12)
        - Garrison
          - David Lloyd 1924-71, undated (Box 104, Folder 13)
          - Ellen Wright 1913-26, undated (Box 104, Folder 14)
          - William Lloyd (1874) and Edith Stephenson 1913-59, undated (Box 105, Folder 1-7)
          - Miscellaneous family 1914, undated (Box 105, Folder 8)
      - Hammond, Dorothea Villard 1925 (Box 106, Folder 1)
      - Harwood
        - Faith Garrison
          - Bliss, Edith Lloyd ("Yoy") 1948, undated (Box 106, Folder 2)
          - Garrison
            - David Lloyd 1924-71, undated (Box 106, Folder 3-6)
            - William Lloyd (1874) and Edith Stephensoncirca 1915-59 (Box 107, Folder 1-3)
            - Miscellaneous family 1920-55, undated (Box 107, Folder 4)
        - Reed 1936-61, undated (Box 107, Folder 5)
      - Krantz, Estella Garrison 1968 (Box 107, Folder 6)
      - Norton
        - Charles McKim 1944, 1948 (Box 107, Folder 7)
        - Garrison 1949, 1958 (Box 107, Folder 8)
        - Martha Hutcheson 1948 (Box 107, Folder 9)
      - Phoutrides
        - Aristides 1915-23 (Box 107, Folder 10)
        - Margaret Garrison
          - "Family" 1927-42 (Box 107, Folder 11)
          - Garrison
            - Agnes 1930-42 (Box 107, Folder 12)
            - Eleanor 1957-58 (Box 107, Folder 13)
            - Eleanor and Frank Wright 1957-58 (Box 107, Folder 14-15)
            - Ellen Wright 1910-30 (Box 108, Folder 1)
            - Frank Wright 1955-58 (Box 108, Folder 2)
            - Margaret Carret 1919-20 (Box 108, Folder 3-9)
            - Miscellaneous family 1919-58, undated (Box 108, Folder 10)
      - Robinson, Katherine Knight Garrison 1940 (Box 108, Folder 11)
      - Valentine
        - Alan 1940 (Box 108, Folder 12)
        - Lucia Norton 1927-48, undated (Box 108, Folder 13)
      - Villard, Henry H. 1940, 1962 (Box 108, Folder 14)
    - Generation 6
      - Gould
        - Anne Garrison 1951-64 (Box 108, Folder 15)
        - James 1960-96 (Box 108, Folder 16)
  - Letters to the Garrisons
    - Acevedo, Pearl 1946, 1959, undated (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Adams
      - Charles Francis 1894-1929 (Box 109, Folder 2)
      - James Truslowundated (Box 109, Folder 3)
      - Nathan 1882 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Ahlborn
      - Emil 1920-42, undated (Box 109, Folder 5-6)
      - Emily 1922-32, undated (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Alcott, Bronson 1863 (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - Alder
      - Charles 1958 (Box 109, Folder 9)
      - Margaret Rachel Bruce "Shibby" 1955-57 (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - Allen
      - Francis, H. 1937-39 (Box 109, Folder 11)
      - Nathaniel 1898 (Box 109, Folder 12)
      - Walter 1904-05 (Box 109, Folder 13)
    - Alter, William 1885-88 (Box 109, Folder 14)
    - Ames
      - Charles Burton 1916 (Box 109, Folder 15)
      - Charles Gordon 1884-95, undated (Box 109, Folder 16)
    - Angell, George T. 1896-1905 (Box 109, Folder 17)
    - Anthony
      - Lucy E. 1905-15 (Box 109, Folder 18)
      - Susan B., [See also Third party correspondence and SERIES IX. WRIGHT FAMILY - Correspondence --Letters to the Wrights] (Box 109)
      - Garrison
        - Ellen Wright Garrison 1881-1905, undated (Box 109, Folder 19-23)
        - Francis Jackson 1891 (Box 109, Folder 24)
        - William Lloyd (1838) 1881-1905 (Box 109, Folder 25-27)
        - Unidentified fragmentsundated (Box 109, Folder 28)
    - Ardle, Lillian W. 1909-24 (Box 109, Folder 29)
    - Astley
      - Frank and Muriel 1923-41, undated (Box 109, Folder 30)
      - F. Lloyd 1923-56 (Box 109, Folder 31)
    - Atkinson, Will J. 1906-07, undated (Box 109, Folder 32)
    - Atwater
      - Abby 1879-92 (Box 109, Folder 33)
      - Richard 1881-90 (Box 109, Folder 34)
    - Avery, Susan Look 1903-09 (Box 109, Folder 35)
    - Axon, William 1890-1907 (Box 109, Folder 36)
    - Ayers, Mary Wilcox 1927-29 (Box 109, Folder 37)
    - Babcock, Katharine 1934-40, undated (Box 109, Folder 38)
    - Baily, Warren Worth 1905-07 (Box 109, Folder 39)
    - Baker, Ray Stannard 1905-07 (Box 109, Folder 40)
    - Barbey, J.A. 1916-23 (Box 109, Folder 41)
    - Barnet, Charles Swasey 1917-18 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Barr, Carolyn ("Shorty") 1926-45, undated (Box 110, Folder 2-3)
    - Barrows
      - Eliza 1909 (Box 110, Folder 4)
      - Isabel 1893-1907 (Box 110, Folder 5)
      - Samuel 1893-98 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Barry
      - Charles Arthur 1916-28 (Box 110, Folder 7)
      - Jane Becket 1920-38 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - Basset, Sara Ware 1944-59, undated (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - Bauduin, Therese and Jean 1947-56, undated (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - Baxter, Philip 1920-38 (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - Beaman, Mary S. 1936-39, undated (Box 110, Folder 12)
    - Beecher, Walter H. 1906-08 (Box 110, Folder 13)
    - Bement, Ruth 1919-74, undated (Box 110, Folder 14)
    - Benson
      - J.C. 1873 (Box 110, Folder 15)
      - Thomas 1899 (Box 110, Folder 16)
    - Berry, Benjamin H. 1904-05 (Box 110, Folder 17)
    - Bird, Margery W. 1922-45, undated (Box 110, Folder 18)
    - Birney
      - George Henry 1888 (Box 110, Folder 19)
      - Laura Stratton 1861-65 (Box 110, Folder 20-21)
    - Blackwell
      - Alice Stone, [See also SERIES VI. SUBJECT FILES - Alice Stone Blackwell Fund]
      - Garrison
        - William Lloyd (1838) 1896-1909 (Box 110, Folder 22)
        - William Lloyd (1874) 1906-48 (Box 110, Folder 23-24)
        - William Lloyd (1874) (Harriet Sewall Trust) 1933-44 (Box 111, Folder 1)
      - Henry Brown 1875-1909 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Blatch, Harriot Stanton 1908-09 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Bolster, Lucy and Richard 1920-29 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Bonney, Frederick P. 1942-43 (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Boutwell, George 1898-1903 (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Bowditch, W.I. 1885-88 (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Bowles, Samuel 1899-1908 (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Boyd, William Riley 1898-1908, [See also SERIES VI. SUBJECT FILES - Race --Education --Forsythe Normal School] (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - Boynton, Theodore 1908-09, undated (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - Bragdon
      - Henry W.
        - Garrison, David Lloyd 1928-44, undated (Box 111, Folder 11)
        - Garrison, Edith Stephensonundated (Box 111, Folder 12)
      - Katherine 1933-38 (Box 111, Folder 13)
      - May ("Aunt Maisie") 1928-38 (Box 111, Folder 14)
    - Braggiotte, Gloria 1928-30, undated (Box 111, Folder 15)
    - Brandt-Erickson, Patsy 1974 (Box 111, Folder 16)
    - Bretz, Harold and Helen 1918-41 (Box 111, Folder 17)
    - Bridgman, Sidney 1892-98 (Box 111, Folder 18)
    - Bromage, Gladys 1926-66 (Box 111, Folder 19)
    - Brown
      - Aliceundated (Box 111, Folder 20)
      - Betty 1935-37 (Box 111, Folder 21)
      - E.R. 1890 (Box 111, Folder 22)
      - Florence A. 1901-13, 1963, undated (Box 111, Folder 23)
      - John, Jr.1886-92 (Box 111, Folder 24)
      - William Wells 1858, 1863 (Box 111, Folder 25)
    - Browne, Francis F. 1904-05, undated (Box 111, Folder 26)
    - Bryce, James 1883-07, undated (Box 111, Folder 27)
    - Buckingham School 1936-39 (Box 111, Folder 28)
    - Buffum
      - Abbyundated (Box 111, Folder 29)
      - James 1886 (Box 111, Folder 30)
      - Lydia 1862 (Box 111, Folder 31)
      - Rebekah Northey
        - Garrison William Lloyd (1805) 1860-61 (Box 111, Folder 32)
        - Garrison, William Lloyd (1838) and Ellen Wright 1862-89, undated (Box 111, Folder 33)
      - Ruth 1864, 1887 (Box 111, Folder 34)
      - William 1855-57 (Box 111, Folder 35)
    - Burleigh, Florence 1907-16 (Box 111, Folder 36)
    - Burr
      - Allston 1900-41 (Box 111, Folder 37)
      - Elizabeth Randolph 1918-32 (Box 111, Folder 38)
      - H.M. 1913-32 (Box 111, Folder 39)
    - Butler, Josephine 1875-90, undated (Box 111, Folder 40)
    - Buxton, Thomas Powell 1841-42 (Box 111, Folder 39)
    - Cable, George Washington 1899-1900 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Call
      - Anne P. 1928-39, undated (Box 112, Folder 2-6)
      - Don 1937-38 (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - Carnighan, M.H. and W.M. 1857 (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - Carret
      - Frances 1926 (Box 112, Folder 9)
      - Georgiana 1904 (Box 112, Folder 10)
      - Grandmother 1926-27 (Box 112, Folder 11)
      - J.F. 1892, 1895, undated (Box 112, Folder 12)
      - Margaret 1874-82 (Box 112, Folder 13)
      - Sarah W. 1892-1918, undated (Box 112, Folder 14-15)
    - Carter
      - Elizabeth C. 1931, undated (Box 112, Folder 16)
      - Frank 1900-02 (Box 112, Folder 17)
      - Franklin Jr. 1903-24 (Box 112, Folder 18)
      - Helen 1895-1900 (Box 112, Folder 19)
    - Catt, Carrie Chapman 1906-47 (Box 112, Folder 20)
    - Chace
      - Eliza G. 1874-86, undated (Box 112, Folder 21)
      - Elizabeth Buffum 1884-99, undated (Box 112, Folder 22)
      - Elizabeth E. 1914 (Box 112, Folder 23)
      - Fenner 1922 (Box 112, Folder 24)
      - Lillie Buffum 1917 (Box 112, Folder 25)
    - Chadwick, John W. 1892-1902 (Box 112, Folder 26)
    - Chamberlain, D.H. 1875-1904 (Box 112, Folder 27)
    - Channing, William Henry 1864 (Box 112, Folder 28)
    - Chapman
      - John Jay 1913 (Box 112, Folder 29)
      - Maria Weston 1884-85 (Box 112, Folder 30)
    - Chase
      - Donald A. 1938-39 (Box 112, Folder 31)
      - Mary C. 1972-74, undated (Box 112, Folder 32)
      - Phillip P. 1928-39 (Box 112, Folder 33)
      - Stuart 1916-29 (Box 112, Folder 34)
      - William Beverly and Edith 1861-62 (Box 112, Folder 35)
    - Cheever, Rev. George B. 1885 (Box 112, Folder 36)
    - Cheney, Ednah Dow 1890, 1897 (Box 112, Folder 37)
    - Chesson
      - Amelia A.E. 1884-99, undated (Box 112, Folder 38)
      - F.W. 1877-87 (Box 112, Folder 39)
      - Fred W. 1888 (Box 112, Folder 40)
      - W.H. 1902 (Box 112, Folder 41)
    - Chestnut, Charles W. 1903 (Box 112, Folder 42)
    - Child, Lydia Maria 1859, 1879 (Box 112, Folder 43)
    - Choate, Joseph 1900-29 (Box 112, Folder 44)
    - Claflin, Jehiel 1884-91 (Box 112, Folder 45)
    - Clark
      - Alice 1898-1946 (Box 113, Folder 1)
      - Bancroft 1928-47, undated (Box 113, Folder 2)
      - Eleanorundated (Box 113, Folder 3)
      - Ellery H. 1933-34 (Box 113, Folder 4)
      - Helen Bright 1879-1918, undated (Box 113, Folder 5-8)
      - Hilda 1901 (Box 113, Folder 9)
      - J. Edmund 1882-85 (Box 113, Folder 10)
      - John Bright 1898-1910 (Box 113, Folder 11)
      - K. 1905 (Box 113, Folder 12)
      - Lucretiaundated (Box 113, Folder 13)
      - Margaret 1900-08 (Box 113, Folder 14)
      - Mariane 1951, undated (Box 113, Folder 15)
      - Mary L. 1938-59 (Box 113, Folder 16)
      - Nathan 1949-50, 1985, undated (Box 113, Folder 17)
      - Peter 1937 (Box 113, Folder 18)
      - Priscilla 1930-31 (Box 113, Folder 19)
      - Roger 1890-1960 (Box 113, Folder 20-24)
      - Rosamond 1972-73 (Box 113, Folder 25)
      - Sarah Bancroft 1899-1966 (Box 114, Folder 1-4)
      - Stephen 1930-46, 1974, undated (Box 114, Folder 5)
      - William 1900-07 (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Clothier
      - Esther Clark 1901-33, undated (Box 114, Folder 7)
      - Thompson 1919-29 (Box 114, Folder 8)
      - Violet and Peter 1943-48 (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Codman, John S 1916-30, undated (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - Coffin, Winthrop and Gertrude 1929-34 (Box 114, Folder 11)
    - Colby, Clara Bewick 1907 (Box 114, Folder 12)
    - Colman, Lucy 1890 (Box 114, Folder 13)
    - Conant, Lucy Scarborough 1883-1906, undated (Box 114, Folder 14-23)
    - Conway, Moncure 1886-1901, undated (Box 114, Folder 24)
    - Cook, Frederick F. 1888, 1899 (Box 114, Folder 25)
    - Cooke, Ruth Emerson 1935-69 (Box 114, Folder 26)
    - Corey, Eva D. 1897-1926, undated (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Cowin, Katherine C. 1922-67, undated (Box 115, Folder 2-3)
    - Cox, C. F. 1888-92 (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Cram
      - Charles E. 1877-1900, undated (Box 115, Folder 5)
      - Mary Wells 1874-1905, undated (Box 115, Folder 6)
      - Robert 1904-42, undated (Box 115, Folder 7-10)
    - Cromwell, Otelia 1934-1954 (Box 115, Folder 11)
    - Crosley, Edith A. 1958 (Box 115, Folder 12)
    - Crosby
      - Eleanor D. 1892, undated (Box 115, Folder 13)
      - Ernest Howard 1897-1905 (Box 115, Folder 14)
      - J.W. 1921-27 (Box 115, Folder 15)
    - Cummings, Philip H. 1946-47, undated (Box 115, Folder 16)
    - Curran, Mary A. Lafferty 1914-17 (Box 115, Folder 17)
    - Cushman family 1900-47, undated (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Cutler, John 1936-39, undated (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Cutting
      - Jim 1929-34, undated (Box 116, Folder 3)
      - R. Bayard 1897-98, undated (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Dahlman, Jane 1932-42, undated (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Dall, Caroline H. 1879-1909 (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - Dalton, Susan 1910-41, undated (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - Daniel
      - Charles 1879-1903 (Box 116, Folder 8)
      - Charles, Jr. 1935-38, 1952, undated (Box 116, Folder 9)
      - Edward 1918-32, undated (Box 116, Folder 10)
      - Kate 1876-1932, undated (Box 116, Folder 11-17)
      - Robert M. 1900-05 (Box 116, Folder 18)
      - Teresa 1887, undated (Box 116, Folder 19)
      - "Yi Yi" 1911-41, undated (Box 116, Folder 20)
    - Davis, Charles Henry 1938-46 (Box 116, Folder 21)
    - Day
      - Fairfield 1928-29 (Box 117, Folder 1)
      - George Parmly 1915-24 (Box 117, Folder 2)
      - Henry B. 1917-30 (Box 117, Folder 3)
      - Joseph 1928-29 (Box 117, Folder 4)
      - Julia 1915-23 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - DeMille, Anna George 1928-40 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Denton, Georgina Kay 1927-28, undated (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - DePierrefeu
      - Dodo 1927-36, undated (Box 117, Folder 8)
      - Elsa Tudor 1935-47, undated, [See also Leland, Elsa Tudor] (Box 117, Folder 9)
      - Katharine 1934-35 (Box 117, Folder 10)
      - Yann 1935 (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - Dickinson, Anna 1907-08 (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - Dickson, Irene 1946-54 (Box 117, Folder 13-15)
    - Dietrick, Louise 1930-45 (Box 117, Folder 16)
    - Dole, Charles F. 1915-28, undated (Box 117, Folder 17)
    - Donald, Malcom 1903-04, undated (Box 117, Folder 18)
    - Douglas, David 1886-1909 (Box 117, Folder 19)
    - Douglass, Frederick 1894 (Box 117, Folder 20)
    - Dreier
      - Ethel 1931, 1956 (Box 117, Folder 21)
      - John 1928-36, undated (Box 117, Folder 22)
    - Dresel, Anna L. 1876-1890, undated (Box 117, Folder 23)
    - DuBois, W.E.B. 1909 (Box 117, Folder 24)
    - Duggan, Mary Alice "Polly" 1930, undated (Box 117, Folder 25)
    - Duncan, Elsa 1927-42, undated (Box 117, Folder 26)
    - DuPont, Deo 1927-31, undated (Box 117, Folder 27)
    - Durham, Meza 1927-28 (Box 117, Folder 28)
    - Duvall, Elizabeth 1973-75 (Box 117, Folder 29)
    - Dwight, Theodore F. 1889 (Box 117, Folder 30)
    - Dyer-Bennet, John 1930-38, undated (Box 117, Folder 31)
    - Eastman, Crystal 1918 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Eaton
      - Elma 1974, undated (Box 118, Folder 2)
      - Peg 1974, undated (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Edison, Thomas A. 1883-94 (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Ehrich, Louis 1896-1909 (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D. 1952 (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Ellis, Allan V. 1918-23 (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Emerson, Fran 1935-38, 1947 (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Endicott, William, Jr. 1876-1909 (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - Epstein, Dena 1957-65 (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - Estlin, Mary 1876-1902 (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - Evans, Rebecca Winsor 1936-53, undated (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - Facio-Lince, Daniel and Nohra1964-71 (Box 118, Folder 13)
    - Fairbanks, Calvin 1865-98 (Box 118, Folder 14)
    - Farrison, W. Edward 1949-52 (Box 118, Folder 15)
    - Fentress, Louise 1928-29, undated (Box 118, Folder 16)
    - Fish, W.H. 1896-1905 (Box 118, Folder 17)
    - Fisher, Iris 1927-30 (Box 118, Folder 18)
    - Flint, Martha E. 1913-29, undated (Box 118, Folder 19)
    - Flynn, Patrick 1904-09 (Box 118, Folder 20)
    - Forbes
      - Allan 1919-55, [See also SERIES VI. SUBJECT FILES- Harvard-- Correspondence] (Box 118, Folder 21)
      - John Murray 1881-95 (Box 118, Folder 22)
    - Foster, Abby Kelley 1883 (Box 118, Folder 23)
    - Fowlds, George 1907-23 (Box 118, Folder 24)
    - Fowler, Francis 1940-46 (Box 118, Folder 25)